Such people will also not get their entry, the
smiley of the bike at the end of the video saying nice madam, nothing like this is going to happen
because guys, it has been a day or two, the
video was not coming automatically
because brother, my scooter met with an accident, look, brother,
one side of the
scooter is not completely visible, guys, it has been completely scratched, talk about
tea here or you can
talk about NDPS or even see the exhaust gas
cost, it has got completely scratched, so we had come after a
proper ride on Sunday Khwaish,
but I don't know where the road was on Sunday night, that is, where the
dryer story, the car got unbalanced, okay
brother, the components that are to be installed inside the sewerage pipe on the side of the road, the
car went completely away and one side will keep peeling, I am
showing you Kabir's Mar Ghat,
see, the way to come till the Marghat will be from this side, the
right to left, I will show you the entire backend of my scooter, if
I talk after giving and taking, then
brother, the right side of the scooter, whatever
part of it is, almost 22, has been damaged,
now I don't know about it.
How much will it cost to repair the alarm? I even went to the
service center to find out if it will be available
for this. Brother said, if something like this happens, it will not be available. Brother
said, if you will face any problem due to scratches, then
you will have to bear the
entire cost from your side. Whatever
increase it may be, I have cleaned the right side and whitened it completely.
Look from here, I have completely cleaned it from the bottom
till one boss, the
silver part on the side is just
yellow black and I will not paint anything on this side. The guys on the
left side,
my entire saver is just on the right side or we used to start
from here, my crematorium has gone and the
most dry damage is visible,
look at this fering where it was
written SSP, you can see it is completely peeled off on the right side, nothing is
visible evenly, it is completely destroyed,
look at it now, and look at this letter which is on the
right, where it broke, here
you will see that the plastic is broken and if we
talk about its test, then look here, it is
attached on this side on the bottom and it was so thick,
AB has peeled off here and
turning a little further back where  Footage has now been
found on this one, scratches and I have
also applied it on this if cost, see, the
total loss of the set from this side is on this side
brother, I am not able to understand what to do,
what not to do, I mean it was a new car, guys,
just a month, just completely white think
and now we are not able to understand
what to do, should I get it done from outside,
from the company, that is what I went to ask, I installed it
here but show it, rather you can see this, it has
completely got damaged but it is safe that nothing has happened to its handle
and if you talk about the indicators side of the
back, then all that
should be visible, thankfully nothing has happened here, not even a single
scratch, this
entire text of side effect is from the walnut here
and it was installed and the Amargarh and
tell me your indicator here, I will
show you the search on this side there, there is nothing there, I have
read and seen
and the guys here are okay now,
look at your set here, it was like this and right now what is happening at Haldi Cross,
this road is absolutely fine,
Marwadi, okay, here on the site that I am
okay, now talk about Delhi  The one with 1042 is also
okay, look here one is okay, I mean it will
come from this side, it did not fall, so it is
absolutely fine here and from the back also okay, now the
condition of the rest of the ride has become bad as you can see,
now look here it is melting,
what should I do, friend, let's get
it changed and the one with the sticker
visible above, I
applied this much, no problem, some
sticker will come here, if it gets tapped then how will it get fixed, the
main problem I am facing is this,
look how bad it is
here, see how it looks, friend,
how much are you setting it, I mean, it happened like this, so
I will see, friend, the company person
said friend, 1112 will take time fifteen sixteen, but he
said it will take time for 11000, so I will see, I will have to get it
changed, it was Sunday but I had
also taken a ride and brother, I had
planned for Monday that I would share the
birthday box with all my friends, there is such a yoga, I mean, I would have
slept, everything would be fine,
but before it gets fine, friend, so much  The big
meaning is fulfilled, what will happen to you, what
cannot happen, I went to that service
center to find out directly, showed it to them that it is like this, so
they said, sir,
don't buy bicycles, it will be done with your own money, I do
n't know, I won't know, what claim is taken at the limit,
maybe lighting, when there is any major
damage, or suppose this part is
available for replacement, the company
insurance people, they will check it, they
can reset it, say, if it fell due to your mistake, then they will
not give any claim, and
for a minor one, I don't know how much it will cost, it is
5,000, even 3,000 will hardly cost, so
they refused to take that much claim, the service center where I went
said, brother, if there is any major
damage to inches, then only in that,
your total cost is borne by the company,
that is due to that, so
I said okay, because they had given additional notice that do
n't take the trouble, get it done from you, it is
minor, it will cost less, I will get it done
somehow, or if it is minor, I
know here, a sticker will be pasted
but this will have to be changed
Get this recognition typed because here
I have asked for it to be changed,
see here you must be seeing this, see it is done,
here my finger is moving, there are
people here, it would be better to get it changed
brother, why angry, this is completely
new and this look goes, it may seem a little rubbish
or a little light, someone might notice all the difference,
I am going to get it changed completely,
now let's see when it will be done, that's why I do
n't understand for a day or two, what should I do, should I make a video,
you people can understand, I mean,
someone has worked with so much difficulty, he has
collected a lot of money, he doesn't have a car for a month
and if something like this happens, can you
understand that there is a problem with that too, I ca
n't explain it to you brother, those who are
interested in bikes, they
spend their entire salary on their car so that the
car looks good and this is the condition of a 1 month old car,
so brother my mind is completely
stopping working on this, I am not able to understand
what to do, what not to do, but okay, I will have to
convince my mind before my heart that if I keep on
taking this in my head, then I will think
what will happen, brother, will I be able to sleep, then I will be fine  What is this to get
repaired under so much tension,
from this year onwards we will not be able to make videos
and there will be only losses, so we will get it
repaired brother, get many clauses of the heart
repaired and everything will be like this first,
you guys don't worry, I will get it
repaired completely, the videos will come as before,
friend, I was thinking and what will happen, I
thought of this Android, I made a new plan that I will
make videos with subscriptions and the first one
also became quite successful, but on the same
day something happened to me that now I am not able to understand anything, my mind was
completely shaken, I am
not able to understand anything brothers what to do, what
not, okay, I will get it repaired,
you should get the update soon brother,
I should get it repaired as soon as possible, I am also
feeling good that my car is in this condition,
friend, it is bad, it is my car, so guys,
I will get it repaired quickly, let's go, it is okay,
you guys, you will get the tension, it will be okay, whatever it
is, it is okay, the good thing is that
it is just the powder, there is
no internal damage to it, whatever it may be, it is a
slight damage on the body, for this, whether it is a few bends,
minute, festival or handling, there is
no problem  The car did not run as it should have, so I
drove it and waited a little, the
view was absolutely center steering and the engine had
power like an hour, there was even one
percent vibration, so
I am quite thankful to their body that
brother, your car is running, okay, the
footer is just damaged, get it repaired,
it is not a matter of much tension, it
feels bad but it is okay, whatever has happened has happened,
now nothing can be done, I will get
it repaired brother, have faith, I will get it repaired,
you guys keep supporting this,
yes brother, what will happen to you after getting it repaired soon, it is
completely
plastic, friend, and let me tell you one more thing, I am getting
angry at the company also, I know
in the previous interview, guys, you must have seen that the
steel
protector, whatever you say, that gas came first, it came from
here, it came from here,
what was here and this one, notice the purest side,
brother, look at any installation, which
you see in the market, active voice and
totka all end drop on the road, notice the two and a half
part which is stitched first  Of base for
entertaining, juice of protector of
Dil company should be steeled here, earlier
you should see it used to be here but
what will the companies do here, they are not giving
its talkativeness from below brother, so here the
volume is low in one thing but I am very angry brother,
you should remove this protector from here in advance, that is a
matter of thinking or right, if
anyone goes from outside then whether this pipe is
installed or not, the protector here is
giving late but not from here, I will not
believe me, so you should
see any vendor, maximum end and when will
you get this point, sheela, don't tell me, it is
not a matter of my comment,
what did you think or not in Adani company, you removed it,
that is the reason today I applied my STD
protector, I know
what happens, I applied it, I saw it in the whole car,
day match, there is peel here, okay, this is
safe, it is the most on this ground, this
boy does not even get on this, even if I apply it, I said
that Nehru and company said 3500, then it is
not going to be of any benefit to me, that is why
I am mixed up, this is my thing
Play the notice voice mail or else
you will go near the notice, you were told the text
maximum the car's noise would have been big now what do you
think company wise people leave this matter
you will get the gas repaired here it is fine then it is done
why do you think by getting tensed I ca
n't do anything there is one thing I should get it
repaired soon so I will get it repaired
I was thinking that I should
make the video it happened on Sunday and today I think it is
Tuesday or Wednesday whenever I thought let me make it
you people will say brother I will
only show you my positive point I would have
shown something connected everything then in my video I
also made the video of that time when
my car met with an accident otherwise
I would
not have brought you directly to the part of getting it fixed but okay I thought let me make it so guys I
made this video enjoy it and get it repaired okay jhaal